She wrote "no way"
on both our cappuccinos.
(Howard:)Poor Bert.
(Howard:)That guy's got a rough
afternoon ahead of him.
(Amy:)Well, how would you want a girl
to tell you she wasn't interested?
(Raj:)I guess, uh, I'd like her to sit me
down, look me in the eye and say,
"I was wrong. I love you."
(Raj:)And then maybe she could
touch me in a special way.
(Howard:)That's how you reject a guy.
(Amy:)Okay, I don't have time for this.
(Amy:)I'm just gonna go find him
and be brutally honest.
(Howard:)-No, don't.
-He'll be so upset.
Hell probably climb
up the Empire State Building
(Raj:)and start swatting at planes.
(Howard:)You want us to talk to him?
(Amy:)Really? You would do that?
(Raj:)Sure. We've both been in his shoes.
(Raj:)We'll let him down with
compassion and respect.
(Sheldon:)-Thank you.
-Let's go.
(Raj:)So we tell him
she's a lesbian, right?
(Howard:)Of course we tell him
she's a lesbian.